Guide to the James Lockhart Autry Family Papers, 1832-1998 MS 003
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Texas, 1875-1998, 148143
  - James Lockhart Autry II, 1859-1920; 148151
    - Sub-Series IV: Personal, 1869-1992, 148785
      - Personal Financial Records, 1881-1919; 149008
        - James L. Autry - Ledger, 1899-1900; 533 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - James L. Autry - Ledger, 1901-1902; 535 (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - James L. Autry - Ledger - Household, Business, 1903; 534 (Box 39, Folder 5)
        - James L. Autry - Ledger, 1916-1925; 531 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Histories - Heroes of Texas: Micajah Autry: A solider of the Alamo, 156185 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Histories - Holly Springs, Mississippi, to the year 1878, photocopy, 1931; 156168 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Histories - I am the family face...an introduction to the Autry Family and the James L. Autry Collection, 1992; 156187 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Histories - Remember the Alamo Heroes, 156186 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Invitations, 1881-1912; 153234 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Memorabilia: Card Announcing James L. Autry's Candidacy for Enrolling Clerk, Texas, House of Representatives, 1880 Dec. 6; 665 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Memorabilia - programs, n.d.; 591 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Newsclippings - James L. Autry, 1920; 149049 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Photographs and Postcards, 148982
        - Autry Family, 1900-1911; 149010 (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Autry Family Residences, 149011 (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - Autry House, Rice Institute, 1921; 149017 (Box 41, Folder 3)
        - Camp Logan, Iowa City, 1910; 149012 (Box 41, Folder 4)
        - Camp Logan, Houston, 149013 (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - Corsicana, TX, 1900; 149014 (Box 41, Folder 6)
        - Friends of Autry, n.d., 149015 (Box 41, Folder 7)
        - James L. Autry, 1874-1908; 149016 (Box 41, Folder 8)
        - James L. Autry, 1912-16; 149018 (Box 41, Folder 9)
        - James L. Autry, Corsicana, 1900; 149019 (Box 41, Folder 10)
        - Lucy "Tap" Waller, 1900-15; 149021 (Box 42, Folder 1)
        - Mexico Trip, 1911; 149022 (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous photographs [627] (includes photograph of one of the last 2 survivors of the Battle of San Jacinto), 1912-14; 149023 (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous photographs, n.d., 149024 (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - Photograph album belonging to James L. Autry, ca. 1866; 149025 (Box 43)
      - Printed Material - Date Book for 1915 [used by James L. Autry to write down memoirs], 153235 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Printed Material - Poem; Author unknown, n.d.; 685 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Printed Material - book belonging to James L. Autry while at St. Thomas Hall including Latin exercises and newspaper clippings on the Know Nothing Party, 631 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Printed Material - Founder's List Subscriptions - To a Fund for the Extension of the University Plan of Education in Texas, 1919; 894; (2 copies) (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Printed Material - Founder's List Subscriptions - To a Fund for the Extension of the University Plan of Education in Texas, 1919; 153236 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Residence: No. 5 Courtlandt Place, 1912-1913; 836
        - Autry House Insurance [822], 1905-1920; 1011 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Household inventory, 1907-14; 149039 (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - New House Plans [510A], 1909-1910; 1265 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - Work Time-Books, 1912; 149041 (Box 44, Folder 4)
        - Lamb-Field Co. Receipts, 1-49, 1912; 840 (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - Lamb -Field Co. Receipts, 50-111, 1912; 839 (Box 44, Folder 6)
        - Lamb-Field Co. Receipts, 112-248, 1912-1913; 838 (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - Work Agreement Between James L. Autry and Lamb-Field Company, Contractor, 1912 March 16; 841 (Box 44, Folder 8)
        - Furnishings, 1912-14; 149040 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Specifications for #5 Courtlandt Place, [ca.] 1912; 842 (Box 44, Folder 10)
        - Estimate and Actual Costs - #5 Courtlandt Place, [1912], 1913; 847 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - Accident Insurance Covering Workers - #5 Courtlandt Place Residence, 1913; 850 (Box 44, Folder 12)
        - Lord & Burnham Co. to James 1. Autry, re: Blueprints, Correspondence Concerning Autry Residence, 1913; 846 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - Blueprint for Window at Stair Landing, ca. 1913; 849 (Box 44, Folder 14)
        - Sanguinet, Staats, & Barnes - Correspondence concerning Autry Residence, 1913; 844 (Box 44, Folder 15)
        - Southern Trust Company to James L. Autry - 1 enclosure, 1913 December 9; 843 (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - Distribution of Costs - Concerning Autry's #5 Courtlandt Residence, ca. 1913; 848 (Box 45, Folder 1)
        - Lighting Fixtures, 1913; 153231 (Box 45, Folder 2)
        - Lamb-Field Co. Receipts, 149-171, 1913; 837 (Box 45, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous Receipts; Lamb-Field Company, [ca.] 1913; 845 (Box 45, Folder 4)
        - Plat Showing Courtlandt Place, [ca. 1913]; 153232 (Box 45, Folder 5)
        - Shrubs and Flowers, 1913-15; 153233 (Box 45, Folder 6)
        - Courtlandt Street Property [678], 1913-1916; 1084 (Box 45, Folder 7)
        - Texas Anchor Fence Co. [635], 1913-1916; 1100 (Box 45, Folder 8)
        - Vacuum Cleaner - Autry House [817], 1914-1920; 1016 (Box 45, Folder 9)
        - Home Furnishings, 1914; 149042 (Box 45, Folder 10)
        - Trees, 1914; 149043 (Box 45, Folder 11)
        - Home Improvements, 1915-16; 149044 (Box 45, Folder 12)
        - Courtlandt Home Title Papers [821], 1916; 1012 (Box 45, Folder 13)
        - Gardener [860], 1914-18; 975 (Box 45, Folder 14)
        - Landscaping, 1916; 149045 (Box 45, Folder 15)
        - Courtlandt Place [775], 1916-1911; 1053 (Box 45, Folder 16)
        - Coal Purchases, 1919; 149046 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Sub-Series V: Autry Estate, 1920-1925; 538
      The materials in this sub-series deal with the administration of James L. Autry's estate: correspondence, financial statements, trust indentures, and personal bequests. Materials are arranged alphabetically by subject.
      - Autry Estate - Accounting - Policy, 1920-1921; 585 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Autry Estate - Administration of Estate, 1920-1923; 149445 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Autry Estate - Automobile Insurance, 1920-1922; 572 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Autry Estate - Automobile Receipts, 1921-1922; 562 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Autry Estate - Autry House [Rice Institute], 1921-1928; 149446 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Autry Estate - Autry Memorial Hospital School, 1923-1928; 149447 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Autry Estate - Bank Statements, 1920-1930; 583 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Autry Estate - Beale Estate, 1920; 149448 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Autry Estate - Bequests Made in the Will to Various People, 1920-1921; 566 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Autry Estate - Bonds and Securities, 1920-1930; 149454 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Autry Estate - Bond Interest, 1922-1927; 149455 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Autry Estate - Fred Brown Claim, 1924; 149470 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Autry Estate - Cemeteries, 1914-1940; 149456 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Autry Estate - Correspondence of James L. Autry, Jr. re: Finances and Investments, 1921-1922; 557 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Autry Estate - Correspondence, J.S. Cullinan, 1920-1927; 149468 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Autry Estate - Correspondence re: Pipeline Lease in Liberty County, 1922; 568 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Autry Estate - Courtlandt Place Property, 1920; 564 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Autry Estate - Donations, 1920-1922; 573 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Autry Estate - Fidelity Trust Company, 1921-1930; 582 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Autry Estate - Financial Inventories of Autry's Income and Expenses, 1908-1919; 581 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Autry Estate - Furnishings, 1914-1953; 149469 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Autry Estate - Garden Furniture, 1914-1935; 149471 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Autry Estate - Garden Furniture Pamphlets, n.d.; 156917 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Autry Estate - Household Matters, 1921-1927; 574 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Autry Estate - Autry Headstone, 1921; 149488 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Autry Estate - Inheritance Tax, 1920-1922; 565 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Autry Estate - Insurance, 1920-1922; 149492 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Autry Estate - Legacies, 1921; 149496 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Autry Estate - Life Insurance Claims, 1920; 571 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Autry Estate - Loans, 1921; 149497 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Autry Estate - Notes Due Estate, 1920-1922; 580 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Autry Estate - Notes of Autry and the Estate, 1920-1921; 579 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Autry Estate - Old River Company, 1921-1922; 559 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Autry Estate - Pedan, Whitney, 1921; 149498 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Autry Estate - Personal Financial Contribution Requests, 1920-1926; 149499 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Autry Estate - Probate of Will and Administration of the Estate, 1920-1922; 567 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Autry Estate - Property Taxes, 1920-1922; 554 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Autry Estate - Property Transactions, 1918-1923; 149500 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Autry Estate - Raywood Canal Company, 1920-1921; 558 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Autry Estate - Real Estate, 1920-1922; 149501 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Autry Estate - Real Estate: Navarro and Liberty County land, 1922-1926; 149502 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Autry Estate - Real Estate: Abstract Title Micajah Autry Survey, Navarro County, September 9, 1923; 149503 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Autry Estate - Real Estate: Leases and Taxes, Navarro County, 1933-1936; 149504 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Autry Estate - Real Estate: Leases and Taxes, Liberty County Acreage, 1937-1938; 149505 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Autry Estate - Real Estate: Leases and Taxes, Liberty County Acreage, 1939; 149506 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Autry Estate - Real Estate: Leases and Taxes, Liberty County Acreage, 1940-1943; 149507 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Autry Estate - Real Estate: Leases and Taxes, Liberty County Acreage, 1944; 149508 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Autry Estate - Real Estate: Leases and Taxes, Liberty County Acreage, 1945; 149509 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Autry Estate - Real Estate: Leases and Taxes, Liberty County Acreage, 1946; 149510 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Autry Estate - Real Estate: Leases and Taxes, Liberty County Acreage, 1947-1952; 149511 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Autry Estate - Receipts and Disbursements, 1919-1920; 149512 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Autry Estate - Receipts and Disbursements, 1923-1925; 149513 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Autry Estate - Repairs and Improvements (Courtlandt St.), 1914-1930; 149514 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Autry Estate - Residential Insurance, 1920-1922; 570 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Autry Estate - Sale of Westmoreland Properties, 1921; 563 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Autry Estate - Securities, 1920-1921; 149515 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Autry Estate - Stocks, 1918-1930; 149516 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Autry Estate - Income Tax Returns & Suits, 1921; 555 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Autry Estate - Taxes, 1920-1925; 149517 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Autry Estate - Travel, Family Cars, 1914-1928; 149518 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - Autry Estate - Trial Balances, 1920- June 1922; 149519 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Autry Estate - Trial Balances, July 1922-1923; 149520 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Autry Estate - Trial Balances, 1924-1926; 149521 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Autry Estate - Trust Indentures, 149522 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Autry Estate - Trust Indentures, 149523 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Autry Estate - Trust Statement Held for Allie May Autry, 1921; 553 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Autry Estate - Ways and Means Statements, 1920-1930; 578 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Autry Estate - Yacht Aloha, 1920-1926; 569 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Jeanie Valliant Autry Brown, 148152
    Separated Materials note
    Removed from the collection are programs from the annual meeting of the United Daughters of the Confederacy from years 1897, 1899-1902, 1904, and 1908. These have been catalogued separately.
    - Various Correspondents to Jeanie V. Brown, 1881-1908; 627 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Jeanie V. Brown to James L. Autry, 1904; 622 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Jeanie V. Brown to James L. Autry, 1907-1909; 620 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Jeanie V. Brown to James L. Autry, 1910; 609 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Various Correspondents to Jeanie V. Brown, 1909-1912; 611 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Jeanie V. Brown Widow's Pension, 1908; 149742 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Newsclippings and Correspondence on Death of Jeanie Valliant Autry Brown, 1912; 149743 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Allie Belle Kinsloe Autry, 1873-1935; 148153
    Removed from the collection is the program from the Salvation Army convention in 1922. This has been catalogued separately.
    Scope and Contents
    This sub-series contains correspondence, personal financial statements, photographs, and memorabilia related to Allie Kinsloe Autry. Also included are materials related to her mother, Katherine S. Kinsloe and other Kinsloe family members.
    - Affiliations and Memberships, 1914-30; 151082 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Autry House Dedication, 1921; 156919 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Balance Sheet, 1926-30; 151084 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Battle Creek Sanitarium, 1913; 151011 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Battle Creek Pamphlets, 156920 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - Marion Logan to Allie Autry, 1903; 151074 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - Allie Autry to James L. Autry, 1904-1905; 623 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - Allie K. Autry to James L. Autry, Jr, 1906; 151075 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - Allie Autry to James L. Autry, 1906-1907; 621 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - Allie Autry to James L. Autry, 1908; 619 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - Allie Autry to James L. Autry, 1909; 616 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Various Friends to Mrs. Allie Autry, 1909; 615 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Carter Pennill to Mrs. Allie Autry, 1909-1910; 612 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - Various Friends to Mrs. Allie Autry, 1910; 608 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Carter Pennill to Mrs. Allie Autry, 1911; 605 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Various Friends to Mrs. Allie Autry, 1912; 603 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - Various Friends to Mrs. Allie Autry, 1912-1913; 600 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Various Friends to Mrs. Allie Autry, 1916-1918; 595 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Business, 1922-28; 151076 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - Personal, 1921-23; 151077 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - Personal, 1924; 151078 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - Personal, 1925-27; 151079 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - Personal, 1928-35; 151080 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - Personal, 151081 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Estate of Mrs. Autry inventories, 1938; 151086 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Houston Negro Hospital Membership, 1930; 149109 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Ledger - Personal Expenses, 1925; 151089 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Ledger - Personal Expenses [loose pages], 1925-26; 151090 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Money Owed to Mrs. Autry, 1920-27; 151094 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Newsclippings, 1922-35; 151096 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Party Plans given by Allie & James L. Autry, n.d.; 589 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Passport, 1929; 151013 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1914-35; 151014 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Personal Checks (blank), 151015 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Photographs - Allie Kinsloe Autry, 1894-1921; 151097 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Photographs - Mrs. Autry and Friends, 1920-30; 151098 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Photographs - Mrs. Autry Gravesite, 1935; 151099 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Photographs - Negatives, 155835 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Photographs - Negatives, 156993 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Receipts, 1920-22; 151100 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Rice Institute Football Poems To Mrs. J.L.A., 1923-24; 155864 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Sympathy Cards, n.d.; 156244 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Travel - Family Vacations, 1914-27; 151101 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Kinsloe Family, 148662
      - Correspondence - H.E. Kinsloe to Allie K. and James L. Autry, 1916; 597 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence - Ralph Kinsloe to Allie Autry, 1902-1929; 624 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence - Mrs. R.H. Kinsloe [Aunt Willie] to Mrs. Autry, 1929-1930; 151139 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Estate of Mrs. H.E. Kinsloe, 1937-1944; 151152 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Kinsloe Newsclippings, 1927-1938; 157012 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Photographs: Dr. Kinsloe, n.d.; 151140 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Photographs: Harris Kinsloe, 151141 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Photographs: Ralph Kinsloe, n.d.; 149029 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Photographs: Mrs. R.H. Kinsloe [Aunt Willie], 151149 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Photographs: Kinsloe Family, n.d.; 151667 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Photographs: Kinsloe Residences-Beaumont and Corsicana, TX, 151151 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Program: Ralph Kinsloe Day, 1928; 157044 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Katherine S. Kinsloe, 1853-1937; 148154
        - Correspondence - Katie Kinsloe to Allie Autry, 1916-1930; 596 (Box 55, Folder 13)
        - Photographs: Katherine S. Kinsloe, 151150 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - James Lockhart Autry III, 1899-1922; 148155
    - Accounts & Income, 1921-1922; 552 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Association of Rice Alumni Newsletters, 1921-1922; 544 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Automobile, 1919-22; 151658 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Camp, 1914-18; 151659 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - F.C. Corps to James L. Autry, Jr., 1912 Feb. 5; 601 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - James L. Autry, Jr. to James L. Autry, II and Allie Autry, 1907-16; 151661 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Business, 1921-22; 546 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - Personal, 1922; 547 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Drafting Set, 149110 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Educational Affairs, 1910-20; 151662 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Estate of James L. Autry, Jr., 1922-23; 151663 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Houston High School Chronicle Aegis, 1916-17; 151664 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Investments, 1920-1922; 551 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Anah Marie Leland Insurance, 1922; 151665 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Life Insurance, n.d.; 550 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Navarro County Ranch, 1921-1922; 549 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Newsclippings, 1922; 151660 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Oil & Gas Information, 1921; 548 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Personal Real Estate Investments, 1922; 545 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Photographs - James L. Autry III, Childhood, 151669 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Photographs - James L. Autry III, Childhood, 157100 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Photographs - James L. Autry III, Childhood, 157101 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Photographs - James L. Autry III, Childhood, 157102 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Photographs - James L. Autry III, 1915-22; 151670 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Photographs - Radio Equipment, 151671 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Photographs - Rice Institute, 1918-22; 151672 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Photographs - Scrapbook Pages (loose), 151673 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Photographs - Negatives, 1921-22; 155832 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Postcards-Large, 156167 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Radio, 1922; 151666 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Rice Institute Commencement and Autry House Dedication Invitations, 1921; 156189 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Statements and Report of the American Smelting and Refining Co., 1920-1922; 543 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Statements and Reports of Various Firms, 1921-1922; 542 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Tax Receipts & Bank Receipts with First National Bank of Corsicana, 1921-1922; 541 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Allie May Autry Kelley, 1903-1998; 148156
    - Address Books, 1970-75; 154084 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Address Books, 1985; 154086 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Address Books, ca. 1986-88; 154087 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Address Books, 1990, 1992-96; 154088 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Address Books, n.d.; 154090 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Allie May and Jane's Chariter Book, 155167 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Autry Court Dedication and Newsclipping, 1951; 154919 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Autry-Kelley Foundation, 1946; 154921 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Autry-Kelley Wedding Register, 1930; 154924 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Birthday/Anniversary Book, 1941-1994; 154089 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Christmas Card Register and Lists, 1925, 1959-1967; 154923 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Condolence Book, Death of Mrs. Allie Kinsloe Autry, 1935; 154091 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Allie May Autry to Mr. and Mrs. James L. Autry, 1908-1918; 617 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - to Allie May Autry, 1910-1930; 606 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - Allie May Autry School Transcripts, 1914-20; 152461 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Allie May Autry, Kent School, 1920-21; 152462 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Allie May Autry to Mrs. James L. Autry, 1924-30; 152463 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - Birth of Edward Kelley, Jr., 1932; 152464 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Birth of Edward Kelley, Jr., 1932; 152465 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - to Allie Autry Kelley, 1932-1995, n.d.; 152466 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - to Allie Autry Kelley, 1932-1995, n.d.; 155249 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - Tejas [Oregon], 1939-47; 152467 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Lynn McCready to Allie Autry Kelley, 1943-1990; 152468 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Black and White Ball, 1957; 152469 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Various Correspondence, 152470 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Various Correspondence - Cards, 152471 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Various Correspondence - Cards, 152472 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Various Correspondence - Cards, 152473 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Various Correspondence - Cards, 152474 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Dance Cards, n.d.; 155168 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Date Books (61) - Oversize, [1930-1989]; 149770 (Box 63)
    - Diploma - Allie May Autry, Houston Public Schools, 1917; 149106 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Floorplan for the Kelley Lounge [Rice University], n.d.; 154922 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Houston High School Commencement Announcements, 1921; 155169 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Interview - Allie May Autry Kelley (DVD-2 copies), October 1, 1994; 162383 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Invitations - Allie May Autry Wedding, December 3, 1930; 155170 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Invitations - Edward Watson Kelley, Jr. and Ellen Elizardi, June 9, 1954; 155171 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Invitations - Miscellaneous, 155172 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Memorabilia - Foreign Currency, 155202 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Memorabilia - Political Convention Tokens [Houston, Texas 1928] and [San Francisco, California 1956], 155177 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Memorabilia - Ration Books [World War Two], 1945; 155191 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Memorabilia - Ration Books [World War Two], n.d.; 157156 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Memorabilia - Rice Institute Commencement, 1925-1926; 156188 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Memorabilia - Ticket Stubs, [1950s]; 155195 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Newsclippings, 154918 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - The Paraders Dance Club Directory, 1952-1953; 154920 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1924-59; 154917 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Photographs - Allie May Autry, Baby, 154129 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Photographs - Allie May Autry, Child, 154130 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Photographs - Allie May Autry - Young Woman, 1920-1925; 154131 (Box 64, Folder 4)